Mm I think you need a dose of Vitamin Me
The scorching heat
Your drooping eyes
You look like you'll fall asleep
You need some of my citrus
A drop that splashed
A squeeze filled with heart
Touching your broken heart
You'll be like oh
One two three
refresh your heart
Zesty Lime juice
I would hate to see you
with a gloomy attitude
Mix up the colors you want
Gulp it down at once
I'll mix it up On a silver platter now
Call it Vitamin ME
Imma make you happy
Sweet Lemon fizz
love it like you do do do do do
Got you feeling new ooh ooh ooh ooh
Imma make you healthy
A growing heartbeat
Sunlight with no night Yes me
Got a boost of Vitamin
ME
Not A,B,C
Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
But you need Vitamin ME
A lukewarm breeze
isn't enough to light up your day
Cause I'm
Feeling you just come alive
I'm the best pick me up that you ever had
Make your lazy heart race
The song you've been longing for, sing along
Like oh
One two three
Refresh your heart
Ruby red grapefruit
I would hate to see you
with a gloomy attitude
Mix up the colors you want
Gulp it down at once
I'll mix it up
On a silver platter now
Call it Vitamin ME
Imma make you happy
Sweet Lemon fizz
Love it like you do do do do do
Got you feeling new ooh ooh ooh ooh
Imma make you healthy
A growing heartbeat
Sunlight with no night Yes me
Got a boost of Vitamin
ME
Not A,B,C
Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
But you need Vitamin ME
Spotlight shining only on you
Secretly I hold your hand
Maybe Maybe you've
Changed Changed me now
Whatever it is with you
This dreamy midsummer
Rising, sparkling
Love it like you do do do do do
Got you feeling new ooh ooh ooh ooh
Fresh and wavy
A growing heartbeat
Sunlight with no night Yes me
Got a boost of Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
Vitamin ME
ME
Not A,B,C
But you need Vitamin ME